https://futureaccess.ca/privacy-policy/

×
Request a Quote
×
HomeDealing with COVIDPortfolioServicesWebsite DesignDigital MarketingGoogle AdsSocial Media ManagementSearch Engine Optimization (SEO)App DevelopmentSoftware DevelopmentGraphic DesignWebsite HostingAboutOur TeamAbout UsThe Future Access ProcessBlogContact
Skip to contentPrivacy PolicyWhat information do we collect?On our website, we collect information from you when you request a quote or fill out our contact form. We do not keep a mailing list nor distribute a newsletter.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:To personalize your experience
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)To improve our website
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)To improve customer service
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)To process transactionsYour information, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating your website, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
